Music
After meeting embaixo-
next week
H youtube.com
Disclaimer
A recording has been dropped.
Now, we will go to...
the last part
or we could combine them everything
let us do this
Today,
24 years starts
pressure
Can you deliver it in time?
I'm Xu Kai.
I use Taobao to buy food.
Delivery is more advantageous.
It's designed fit for these long distance
So
But he still female
who
do you
what's wrong
do you have instructions
No
Missata I heard wrong
I'll wait for you outside.
The city of Chang'an is full of evil and evil.
But every time I approach the whole city,
all the traces are invisible.
It's hard to touch.
What is behind this?
Why isn't Boss back yet?
Did he find it?
Boss, how is it?
Can you stop being so stubborn?
Sit down.
How can I sit down?
That old monkey sent a little monkey to ask us how we are doing.
These demons can't wait any longer.
They are waiting for you to make mistakes.
If we don't find the Buhua Valley quickly,
I'm afraid we'll be in trouble.
Who is it?
Boss, what's wrong?
Uncle.
What's wrong?
The demon is a law.
The Buhua Valley is being destroyed.
We have to destroy it quickly.
And give Si Men an explanation.
Si Men.
If we don't stop the second attack,
we'll be out of demons.
Four Elders, should I help you?
This is...
This is not resentment.
It's murder.
That's right.
This is not an ordinary Buhua Valley.
It's his.
Whose?
It's him.
Eighteen years ago,
he killed the Ghost Eagle.
I'm sorry.
Old man,
it's great to see you.
This mountain house is too big.
I'm lost.
Do you know which way is the way down the mountain?
You don't recognize me anymore?
I know.
Have we met before?
Mother?
Why are you here?
We haven't seen each other for three years.
Son,
I miss you every day.
Good boy.
I miss you too.
Mother.
I miss you every day.
I miss you, mother.
I miss you so much, mother.
Mother.
This mortal
is so easy to fool.
It's a pity
that there are fewer people here.
If I can enter Chang'an City,
I can practice
and have fun.
I think
it will be fun.
Ha ha ha.
Wow,
it's a safe house.
It's so clean.
Why did you
separate the old books and write new ones?
I'm sorry
for not being able to do so.
The latest files.
These are also important.
What case?
It's said that a villager from the West Coast
climbed up the mountain to chop firewood.
He got lost.
Although his family finally found him,
he was not normal.
Not normal?
In short,
he was staring at something,
but he lost consciousness.
He lost consciousness,
but he was smiling.
He kept saying,
Mom, mom.
But his mother died of illness.
Where did the villagers get lost?
West Coast.
What's wrong?
Just a month ago,
the Sword-Picking Bureau has received six files.
The villagers climbed up the mountain to get lost.
They are all from the West Coast.
I'll go and investigate as soon as possible.
No need.
Minister Xu has sent Fuli and others to investigate.
There will be news soon.
The mountain road is hard to walk.
It will take a while.
My feet are painful.
It's harder than going to the office.
How about going back?
Yes.
Minister Xu didn't take it seriously.
He sent us here
just to have a look around.
I don't have to be so serious.
All right, all right.
We're here.
At least we can see it clearly.
If there's nothing to see,
we'll go back and report it.
In my opinion,
the villagers are just lost.
If we don't take it seriously,
they might have eaten something poisonous
and had hallucinations.
I think so, too.
And if they are not easily lost,
we'll be more likely to be lost.
There's another stupid thing.
Look.
Who told you that it's cloudy these days?
How come there is so much fog here?
Don't walk.
There's no way to go there.
Where are we going?
Zhao Hualiu.
I'm sorry to bother you.
We are from the Xuanjian Bureau.
We came to investigate this case.
We are very confused.
May I ask...
I can't believe it.
This is not right.
This...
This is...
Could this be the body of the deceased
who died a few days ago?
I don't know.
Could this be the body of the deceased
who died a few days ago?
They seem to be strange.
Are they really human?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Who can tell?
They are innocent.
What the hell?
How about...
Let's go and have a look.
Are you lost here?
Can you hear me?
Hurry up!
What?
You said you would help me?
You are so big now.
Are you afraid that the demon will not notice you?
I will take you away.
Then you will be safe.
You are a member of the demon clan?
You are in the West suburb.
You are in Chang'an.
The demon clan will know soon.
The demon clan will attack.
You can't escape.
I came to report
to help you.
Help me?
Why do you need to help me?
I help you
because you can help me.
Why does it seem that
the book of Heaven and Fire
is missing from the 18 years of
the book of Heaven and Fire?
40.
I am sorry.
What is it?
I have sorted the files
in the dark library.
Please have a look.
No need.
I am relieved.
But I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
There is something missing from the files.
It is about the 18 years of the book of Heaven and Fire.
Really?
Then what?
There are many old files
that have not been solved.
Maybe we can get some clues
from the files.
It is not necessary to find out
how old you were 18 years ago.
There are some cases
that have been solved for too long.
No need to bother about them.
The officials should solve the problems
for the people and the people.
There is a dark library in the palace.
People often send people to search for the files.
Maybe the file you mentioned
was borrowed by the palace.
What should we do?
You can't do anything.
You want to get something from the palace?
You are not qualified to be a secretary.
Even if I am the secretary of the Xuanjian Bureau,
I can only go to the palace
once a month
to get the files.
What are you thinking?
Secretary?
What is it?
Secretary!
Something bad happened!
Well, sir.
No Equipment
新海非斯基底驱蟹洗发水控油水扬酸。
配方深入基底。海非斯邀您精彩继续。
这是发生了何事?
唉,就是那西郊的案子。
徐司使不是派人去查了吗?
是去过了,可他听完情况就说不管了。
但是今天,有西郊的村民进入长安, 下跪求求。
这案子到底是由哪里进行的?
还没有定论,就惊动了柳尚书。
总之,就按阿叔说的,交代给朱营便好。
猫公用起我的副手来,倒也顺手。
开门!
让我们在这里开门!
徐兰,参见柳尚书。
徐司使,本官今日唤你前来,所谓何事?
想必你也清楚了吧?
唉,下官愚钝。
除了西郊案,还能是何事?
西郊案?那不应该归衙门查吗?
半月之内,足有六名村民于山中迷路失踪。
之后虽被找到,却睁眼无名,神志不清。
此事诡异,不合常理。
目归你玄剑司,归谁呀?
那这六人现在情况如何?可有性命之忧啊?
所有人如今都已苏醒。
六尚书,玄剑司所查的都是毫无头绪之案。
这六人现已苏醒,你便多了六个证人,应赶快缉拿真凶。
什么长按追凶啊?你的意思让我缉拿那误气归案吗?
山中多余,有些误气是正常的。
倒是你们身为父母官,理应为百姓做一些路标,路牌指路啊。
那几人的祖辈皆是西郊之人,山中如同他们家后院。
敢问徐司使,你会在自己府中迷路吗?
也不是没有这个可能。
胡说八道,你听我。
宣成,以你的意思,衙门是查不了这个案子是吧?
左一个查不了,右一个接不了。
你等都这般推尾怕事,挑挑拣拣。
难不成要本尚书亲自去查吗?
尚书息怒。
那现如今,你们准备怎么办?
你。
柳尚书。
是你那小郎君。
梅家郎君。
柳尚书。
免礼。
梅家郎君,你有何事便说吧。
回柳尚书,西郊福员辽阔,宣建司人手不足,调查此事有心无理。
此事若再有旁案,怕是难以两全。
但这件事确实难以以常理存夺。
若交衙门处理,一时也是无从下手。
那这。
因此,下官有以两全之计,或可破此难题。
是何计策?
属下任宣建司暗读库主事一职。
此事卷宗整理妥善,正是闲事。
不妨让下官前往西郊,探查此事。
住口!
尚书,我。
此事凶险万分,你千万不可正讲,听我的话,快走。
多谢徐司使关心,属下心意已决,司使不必再劝。
柳尚书意下如何?
柳尚书,梅主事。
现在宣建司上下已忙得不可开交,抽调不出人手协助你了。
这事就算了。
属下一人前去即可。
梅家郎君,你可想清楚,不后悔了?
绝不后悔。
你这小郎君倒是不忌讳,和其他人不同啊。
他是胆子大一些。
孝臣,别发愁了。
怎么能不愁?
谁知道当年的邪煞还残留了一块骨头在外头。
虽说我不记得十八年前是何情况,
可也曾听说那邪煞鬼影甚是厉害。
只身浅了,却不知何时才出现。
这些都是我所知的。
只身浅来长安,造成人间大崩,
又差点颠覆了妖师。
若不是前任猫公一命相搏,只怕妖师也。
他回来了。
猫公大人。蛇公大人。
小猪营,好久不见。
可是有雷金木的消息了。
他猜得对。
在何处?
西郊。
再具体点。
山洞。
二叔,你再仔细讲讲雷金木。
雷金木天生地长,
为吸取天雷所生之灵物,
亦能驱除不化骨的杀气。
但是,寻常妖怪,根本无法接近。
如此说来,这活儿倒是为我量身打造的。
只要我在白日人参时接近,便能取得那雷金木。
可你白日里并无法力。
只身前五西郊太过冒险。
要不我们……
进一趟山而已,没什么大不了的。
小真。
我明日便去,取那雷金木。
郎君真的要去啊?
要去哪里?
可人家都说那西郊山里不干净。
放心吧,没事的。
你们这玄剑寺也太不够意思了。
人人都下成那样,一个陪你去的都没有。
是我一意孤行,怪不得他人。
家里还有多少银钱?
总的大体三十块。
好。
郎君这是有心凑聘礼,向清禾县主提亲了?
你那么高兴,从前不是不喜五娘子吗?
可是这些日子我也算看明白了。
这清禾县主虽说有顽固之名,却也不怎么发脾气。
还懂得欣赏我做的吃食,挺好自豪的。
最重要的就是,郎君穷,可是他有钱啊。
你们两人在一起,很是相配。
我来的路上听闻,你家门口是条破路。
又长又窄又泥溺,马车都进不去。
这陛下赐的车也真是的,需要两匹马才能拉。
知道你今日休没,便过来找你玩。
没曾想,你家门口这路是这么烂。
我这一路走来,脚也崴了,鞋也脏了。
你说怎么办吧?
这条路一宁不平,捉是不便。
我从玄建司预制了一些月风。
这两日,你找人修一修吧。
原来郎君最近一直存钱,是为了修路啊。
还有,把这棚也拆了吧。
棚子?驴棚怎么办?
这,这要拆了的话,咱家富贵住哪儿啊?
给他换个地方,这路太窄,无法驾车而入。
可,可也不至于将驴棚拆了吧。
咱们驴车小,使劲挤挤,也能进来。
就拆了吧,毕竟有的马车,不似那般精致可爱。
这。
别吃了,走。
阿姐让你们来的吧?
阿姐,你怎么来了?
华阳林渊。
到。
见过县主。
又是明庄跟宫里告的状吧?
我去城外玩一两天也不是头回了。
阿姐派你们过来干嘛呀?
回县主,今日城外不太平。
皇后娘娘是县主性的绝将,怕是不会改变形成。
她特拜属下二人下来保护,还望县主见谅,莫让属下难做。
您俩让我难做了。
县主说什么?
我说,当着我坐骑了。
到家了,到家了,快醒醒啊,到家了。
醒醒啊,醒醒啊。
公主,快救救我们吧。
那何三身子还没好呢,今早又晕了两个。
还是咱们村最强壮的。
是啊。
这位官人,上面到底是什么意思呀?
我们这一村子的人全都是靠着砍柴打猎为生的。
这下,个个都不敢进山了。
我和我们的日子可怎么过呀?
是呀,没过呀。
待我进山探个究竟,必会给大家一个答复。
你别开玩笑了你。
能救你这小身马?
一个人进山?
他也是被关了来。不知道人多危险,还绷在狗里呢。
怕是都出不来了。
是啊。
是啊,这官家公主都不想管我们了。
谁说官府只派了他一个人?
你是谁呀?
五国公府清河县主武珍。
特来助梅主事破西郊悬案。
清河县主?好像是皇后的妹妹。
是啊。
那可是皇亲国戚呀。
就算是派一个县主,又有何用啊?
除了名头大,不还是一个小娘子吗?
你看。
小娘子又如何?
论品级,她也不像皇后的妹妹。
她是皇后的妹妹。
她是二品质,她比很多人的儿子更高位。
她非常厉害。
她是中康中的徐三郎,她是上庭中的张将军。
她是临冲的郭郎军。
她是金吾卫的王祖磊。
她是谁呀?
她是我的敗将。
她是什么人呀?
那是她。
她听着很名头大。
那是她的强大力量。
Really?
It should be quite impressive.
Right.
There are two more Jin Wuwei here.
His Majesty and Her Highness personally arranged them.
In a while, they will help you get a famous doctor.
If you don't believe me, you can check the cards.
Then how about I go and check?
I'll go and check.
Let's go.
Is it true?
It's true.
It's really Jin Wuwei.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
We three are just here to help.
We are far from being compared to the Mei Zhu Shi beside you.
This...
But this gentleman is so gentle and gentle.
So what?
This...
We have martial arts skills, but we can't cut the case.
Mei Zhu Shi is different.
Mei Zhu Shi is a civil official.
He has a wide range of knowledge and knowledge.
He is talented and has a lot of experience.
This time, we will definitely find out the case.
If that's the case,
that would be great.
I heard that Mei Zhu Shi found out the case.
He is weak and delicate.
He needs to speed up his progress.
He just wants to see the merchant city soon.
We are very impressed.
Sir, this is Jin Shan.
You must be careful when you enter the mountain.
Yes, you must be careful.
Thank you.
If my sister asks,
tell her that the Mei Zhu Shi is weak.
I'm worried that he will enter the mountain alone.
Mei Zhu Shi, don't cross the bridge.
The Mei Zhu Shi is a civil official.
Thank you, Mei Zhu Shi, for your help.
I should thank you for helping me.
Please remember to show your kindness to me.
Why did you go to the west?
You said it.
For your safety,
I'm weak.
I'm afraid I'll be dead in an hour.
And I was still alive at that time.
I must save you.
I thought you would drive me away.
It's true.
But I can't find any other reason
to become your lover.
Luckily, I helped you in time.
That's why I blocked your mouth.
You said they were your
defeated champions.
Is it true?
Of course.
They all beat me.
No one beat me.
Why?
They offended you?
No. They went on a blind date with me.
No one can make me look good.
I see.
But why didn't you care about me?
You won by winning several times.
You can win with a chain.
Don't compare yourself to them.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
I'll be with you.
Everything will be fine.
Mr. Shu,
I haven't seen the Seven Devils for days.
I've been searching for them
but I didn't see the shadow of the Shuyao.
Why don't you ask the owner of the house
or go to the inner gate of your house
and see if there are any other clues?
Mr. Shu,
are you sure you've searched everywhere?
Mr. Hui,
if you divide the four doors into eight rooms,
the owner of the house will be in charge of the rooms.
The one who can't decide
will be handled by the owner of the four doors.
will have to make a decision.
I'm helping you
because we're close.
I'm here to ask for your responsibility.
You're here to force me.
I'm afraid it's against the rules.
No.
How dare I offend you?
There are demons who disappear for no reason.
I can't afford to take the responsibility.
It seems that we should find the cat master
and let him make the decision.
Mr. Hui,
are you saying I'm not worthy of it?
Mr. Shu,
why do you say that?
We have no idea about this matter.
According to the rules,
we shouldn't report to the second master.
The cat master has been busy recently.
Don't bother him with such a small matter.
I'll walk around the demon's room
and help you find the cat master.
Thank you, Mr. Shu.
Mr. Shu has been friends with the cat master for many years.
He grew up with him.
He taught him the practice of the demon's method
and helped him manage the demon's world.
They have different relationships.
But I also want to advise you
that the demon's world is the demon's after all.
The cat master is a half-demon.
You're always smart.
Don't let your loyalty delay your future.
Thank you for your reminder.
Goodbye.
I thought
I'd get to know you after you're old enough.
I also want you to enjoy your life here.
But you've grown up.
You're not young anymore.
I'm not the one to blame.
You shouldn't have
gone to Lin Xiao's stupid place.
It's a big trouble for Xiao Zhen.
But I'll give you a good ending.
The demon's elixir has been hit by the cat master.
You're dead.
Don't kill me.
The Demon's World
I didn't expect
we'd be back to life
in this wilderness.
We're here at the right time.
Young Master.
The Demon's World
Is it pretty?
Yes.
Make yourself at home.
Good night.
Well,
I wonder
if there's more than two flows with you each day seen.
Of course.
I've seen something like this before.
You're really a smart man.
This is a mysterious object.
It's a human crystal.
It's a shampoos.
When facing this kind of thing,
most people don't care.
But once it's infected,
it will get sick.
It seems...
It seems this is what the Xuanjian Temple is looking for.
I heard from someone in Quzhou
that they want to remove this kind of thing
and find the root.
Just remove it.
You've learned a lot in Quzhou.
Wuniangzi,
there's a danger ahead.
You...
You're still here.
Since you're not in good shape,
just keep your eyes closed.
Dr. Wang
Other side.
The mountain is overgrown with the mountains, but fortunately it's scattered.
But I don't know why you didn't ask me how to get here.
You're too fast. I can't ask you.
So why didn't you ask me?
I've already left. Why would I ask you again?
I can't leave you alone.
And this road might be too narrow for you.
I'll go with you.
I'll be here.
Thank you.
I think we're heading to the base of the tent.
I just think the view is nice.
I didn't expect you to be so good.
It's hard to walk. Be careful.
Are you okay?
You're so stubborn.
Come up.
I'm sorry.